你居然还活着
You're...freakin' alive.
到底发生了什么
What the hell happened?
迪克爆炸时我们站得太近了
Standing too close to exploding Dick
被炸进了炼狱
sends your ass straight to purgatory.
过了整整一年  你怎么逃出来的
For the whole year? Well, how'd you get out?
走过的路
你好  迪恩
Hello, Dean.
你到底是怎么出来的
How the hell did you make it out?
你好  卡西迪奥  我叫娜奥米
Hello, Castiel. My name is Naomi.
我们救了你
We rescued you.
-地狱之门  -地狱之门怎么了
- Hell gates. - What about hell gates?
碑上讲了如何
The tablet told me all the stuff about
永远关上地狱之门
closing the gates of hell forever.
她叫艾米利亚・理查森
Her name's Amelia Richardson.
我们在德克萨斯州的科米特有个住处
She and I had a place together in Kermit, Texas.
-做什么呢  -我准备走了
- What are you doing? - I'm leaving.
-什么  -我只是想做我该做的
- What? - I'm just trying to do the right thing here.
你和唐该再试一次
You and Don deserve a chance.
-迪恩・温彻斯特  -你是天使吗
- Dean Winchester? - You're an angel?
我真名叫萨曼德里奥
My name is Samandriel.
还有碑文
There are more tablets?
不只是利维坦和恶魔
More than "Leviathan" and "Demon"?
想想那些无辜的生命
These are innocent lives we're talking about.
你愿凭本尼的一面之词冒险吗
And you're willing to risk that on Benny's word alone?
我当然会
Damn right I am.
胳膊别乱动  邪恶的东西
Lay down your arms, you unholy thing!
你想怎么样
What do you want?
我要把你的脑袋插在桩子上
I want your head on a stake.
干完了吗
Is it done?
-没错  -有人伤亡吗
- Yeah. - Any casualties?
-马丁死了  -是本尼吗
- Martin. - Was it Benny?
他自找的  萨姆
He had it coming, Sam.
如今
娜奥米
Naomi.
娜奥米  克劳力抓住了我
Naomi, Crowley has me.
-用天使电台了  是吗  -没有
- Been on angel radio, have we? - No.
别对我撒谎  阿尔菲
Don't lie to me, Alfie.
我没有撒谎
I'm not lying.
求求你  我不会对你说谎的
Please, I wouldn't lie to you.
阿尔菲  这都几个星期了
Oh, Alfie, after all these weeks together.
我真希望你不是在说谎
I mean, how -- how I wish that were so.
现在我们只能...
Now we're going to have to...
再一次
Turn off that signal...
关掉信号
Again.
不
No.
不要
No!
不要啊
N-o-o-o-o-o-o!
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十集
得克萨斯州  克米特
撕 毁 磨 碎
你以为是谁
Who did you expect?
开了很久吗
Long drive?
如果不是你挂了我的电话
Well, I wouldn't have had to make it
我也不用急着赶回来
if you hadn't have hung up on me.
是啊  我已经听到我需要知道的了
Yeah, well, I heard all I needed to hear.
不  你只是听到了你想听的
No, you heard what you wanted to hear.
我都说了本尼没有杀人
I told you Benny wasn't killing.
我亲眼看他杀了那个在干坏事的吸血鬼
Hell, I watched him end the fangbanger that was.
那马丁呢  他是怎么死的
How about Martin? How did he end that?
笨死的  跟我说的一样
Stupid -- just like I said it would.
是那疯子逼本尼的
Crazy son of a bitch didn't give Benny a choice.
那是正当防卫
It was self-defense.
真的吗  迪恩
Seriously, Dean?
就用这种话来糊弄我吗
That's the story you're going with?
说那个吸血鬼才是受害者
That the vampire was the real victim here?
不管你爱不爱听  这是事实
Hey, like it or not, that's the truth, okay?
以前你不会不相信我的
There was a time when that actually meant something.
是啊  可不是嘛
Yeah, yeah. No kidding.
你什么意思
What does that mean?
你以为我只是为了本尼的事吗
You think this is just about Benny?
你在扯什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
你以为呢
What the hell do you think I'm talking about?
艾米利亚
Amelia?
拜托  老弟
Oh, come on, man.
我给你发那条短信是想让你...
I sent you that text 'cause I needed you to -- to --
你想让我什么
You needed me to what?
屁颠屁颠跑去德州
To tear ass to Texas?
让我担心发生在杰西卡身上的惨剧
To be afraid that what happened to Jessica,
发生在所有我们在乎的人身上的惨剧
what happened to... everybody that we care about
在她身上重演
might have happened to her?
你要去杀了本尼  你让我怎么办
You were gonna kill Benny. What was I supposed to do?
我们现在就这样吗
Is that what we are?
你为了救一个吸血鬼
You save a vampire
就骗我让我以为我爱的人有生命危险
by making me believe that the woman I love might be dead?
你想听我说什么  萨姆
What do you want to hear, Sam?
想听我认错吗
That I was wrong?
好吧  我错了  好吗
Fine. I was wrong. Okay?
但你当时如果能听我说完
But if you'd have just heard me out,
如果你能相信我
if you'd have trusted me,
所有这一切都是能避免的
all of this could have been avoided.
你不是让我相信你
You didn't want me to trust you.
你是让我相信本尼  我做不到
You wanted me to trust Benny, and I can't do that.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  那我们现在该干什么
Okay, well, then, what the hell do we do now?
看情况
That depends.
看你的情况了
It depends on you.
看你和他还有没有关系
On whether or not you're done with him.
说实话  我不知道
Well, honestly, I don't know.
很高兴来跑一趟
Glad I made the drive.
他已经哭了两天了
He's been crying for two days.
医生忽视了一件事
The doctors missed something.
这是腹股沟疝  很难发现
It's called an inguinal hernia -- very hard to detect.
卡西迪奥  有情况了
Castiel, we have a situation.
萨曼德里奥被抓住了
Samandriel has been captured.
我还以为萨曼德里奥已经死了
I thought Samandriel was dead.
他失踪了
He's been missing,
现在我们知道了  克劳力抓住他了
and now we know -- Crowley has him.
-在哪  -我还没来得及定位
- Where? - His distress call cut out
他的呼救就被打断了
before I could pinpoint his exact location,
但你得找到他  并把他带回家来
but you will find him and you will bring him home.
这次克劳力一定会严防天使
Crowley will have warded against angels this time.
我得找人帮忙
I'll need help getting in.
需要什么就带什么
Take whatever you need.
但有一点你得记住
But you will be certain, Castiel,
营救萨曼德里奥是你自己的主意
it was your idea to rescue Samandriel,
与我和天堂无关  明白吗
not mine, not heaven's. Do you understand?
该死的  小卡
Damn it, Cass!
我和你说过多少次了
How many times I got to tell you...
太吓人了
...it's just creepy!
迪恩  我需要你帮忙
Dean, I need your help.
天使萨曼德里奥
The angel Samandriel...
-萨  -被抓住了
- Sam-- ...- He's been taken.
你是说阿尔菲吗  那个香肠店的孩子
You mean Alfie, the wiener-on-a-stick kid?
没错
Yes.
我今天早上听到他呼救了
I -- I heard his distress call this morning.
在天使电台上听到的吗
On what, angel radio?
你不是给关上了吗
I thought you shut that down.
我的苦行赎罪进行得很好
Well, my penance, it's going well,
我觉得可以重新打开了
and I thought it was time to turn it back on.
我  一直在帮助别人  迪恩
I've, uh...been helping people, Dean.
算你好样的  好吧
Well, good for you. All right.
那是谁抢走了天堂最可爱的天使
So, who snatched heaven's most adorable angel?
克劳力
Crowley.
继续说
I'm listening.
萨曼德里奥被关在
Samandriel is being held in the
内布拉斯加州  哈斯丁附近
general vicinity of Hastings, Nebraska.
附近  只知道这些吗
"The general vicinity"? That's all you got?
没错  所以我需要你帮忙
Yes, which is why I need your help.
看起来这件事需要
It seems this is gonna involve...
和人们沟通
talking to people.
小卡  我以为现在你是个猎人了呢
Come on, Cass, I thought you were a hunter now.
我之前也这么以为  不过
I thought so, too, but...
-我似乎缺乏一些  -能力
- it seems I -- I lack a certain -- - Skill?
你什么都没看到
You saw nothing.
好了
All right.
我要找什么呢
What am I looking for?
天使受到折磨的时候
Well, when you torture an angel,
他会喊叫  而那种痛苦
it screams, and that kind of pain,
产生奇怪事件的连锁反应
it creates a ripple effect of strange incidents.
萨姆在哪里
Where's Sam?
萨姆走了
Sam's gone.
没事  我们自己也能找到阿尔菲
It's all right. We'll, uh, find Alfie ourselves.
这只可爱的小金龟子
This charming little dung beetle
在埃及的沙漠上生活
makes his living upon the sands of Egypt.
在这里  无数微小的沙粒
Here, billions of tiny particles,
无尽的撒哈拉之风
the remnants of ancient seas,
将这片古海的遗址越推越高
are pushed ever higher by the relentless winds of the Sahara.
金龟子就在这里生存
This is where the dung beetle makes its living.
古埃及人
The ancient Egyptians...
昨晚在酒吧里
Look, last night at the bar,
我只是想确定那是你
I just wanted to make sure it was you.
就是往我家窗子里偷窥的那个
You know... peeping in my window.
偷窥
"Peeping."
你怎么说的那么像
You make it sound so, uh...
跟踪狂
Stalker-ish?
总之  我跑出去是因为他要走了
Anyway, I ran out because he was leaving.
他回来后  经常去旅行
He travels a lot since he's been back.
好  我懂的  你必须得
Right, n-no, I get it. You had someplace...
去一趟
I had to be, yeah.
你打算一直让我
Are we gonna have a whole conversation
替你说完话吗
with me finishing your sentences?
你怎么会来
So, why are you here?
不是你想的那样
It's not what it looks like.
我以为你遇到麻烦了
I-I thought you were in trouble...that you had...
不重要了  你没事就好
It doesn't matter. You're okay.
我之前是没事
I was okay.
安定下来  我很满足
You know, settled in...content.
但是你来了
But here you are.
我该怎么办呢
What am I supposed to do with that?
给我五秒钟  我立刻消失
Give me five seconds, and I'll be gone.
我不是来给你添麻烦的
I didn't come here to make trouble for you.
-我来是因为  -你在乎
- I-I came because... - You cared?
你瞧
See that?
我又那么做了
I just did it again,
替你说完你要说的话
finished your sentence.
是的  我在乎
Yeah, I care.
我也在乎
I care, too.
我说了那只是意外
I told you it was an accident.
是的  当然了
Yes, of course.
但现在就不会再发生意外了
But now there shall be no more accidents,
再也不能用天使无线电了
no more angel radio.
停下吧  求你了  都已经
Stop this, please. It's been...
好几周了  是的
...weeks, yes.
可我就快成功了
We're almost there, though.
我十分确信
I'm certain of it.
我求你了
I'm begging you!
当我们恶魔附身人类时
When we demons possess a human,
我们会侵入他的全身
we invade all of them.
肌肉  骨骼  还有大脑
Their muscles, their...bones, their brains.
不知道天使是不是也是这样
I can't help but wonder if it isn't the same for angels.
不要
No.
[天使语]
Vah-teh-kah-rah.
Sal-voch-tay.
[天使语]
Vah-teh-kah-rah.
Sal-voch-tay.
[天使语]
Sal-voch-tay!
内布拉斯加州  日内瓦
辛克利先生
Mr. Hinckley?
我们是《日内瓦公报》的
Hi. Uh, we're from the, uh, Geneva Gazette.
我想问你几个关于你被"树袭"的问题
I wanted to ask you a few questions about your ambush.
我真想笑
Yeah, well...I'd laugh, too,
可我的脸感觉像是被太阳啃了
if it didn't feel like the sun just ate my face.
那是个比喻
It's a metaphor.
抱歉  在警方的报告中
Sorry. Uh, now, in the police report,
写到灌木对你说话了
it said that the, uh -- the bush talked to you, yeah?
是的  我知道听起来很疯狂  但的确是
Yeah, I know it sounds crazy, but, yeah.
它说了什么
And what did it say?
克林贡:《星际迷航》中假造的一个好战外星种族
不清楚  听起来就像克林贡语
No clue. Sounded like Klingon to me.
我们需要确切的词语
Gonna need exact words.
你说真的
Are you serious?
他这表情不是在开玩笑
That's his serious face, yes.
记得多少就说多少吧  辛克利先生
As much as you can remember, Mr. Hinckley.
听起来像是
Sounded something like...
[天使语]
"Sol-voch."
是的  [天使语]
Yeah. "Sol-voch-tay."
你怎么看  懂那是什么意思吗
Well, what do you think? Mean anything to you?
是的  是天使语  意思是服从
Yes. It's enochian. It means "Obey."
-服从  服从什么  -我不知道
- "Obey"? Obey what? - I don't know.
但那个天使肯定很痛苦
But the amount of pain an angel must be in
他不仅通过灌木显灵还点着了它
not just to manifest through shrubbery but to burn --
迪恩  我们要赶快找到他
Dean...we have to find him before it's too late.
好的
Okay.
既然都出了这样的事
Okay, well, look, a sign like that --
阿尔菲肯定就在附近  对吧
Alfie can't be too far, right?
那我们就从那灌木丛开始寻找答案
So we'll just start at the bush and work our way out.
到底寻找什么
And look for what exactly?
克劳力可能把他藏在任何地方
Crowley could have him anywhere.
如果我是克劳力
Well, if I know Crowley,
那地方一定聚集着一堆恶魔
the place will be swarming with demons.
所以我们一走  直到遇见它们
So we'll just drive till we see ugly.
我决定了  我不喜欢旅馆
It's official -- I hate motels.
说话呀
Say something.
你想让我说什么
What would you like me to say?
感觉很棒  还是说这是不对的
"That was great"? "That was...a mistake"?
我不知道  或许都是
I don't know. Both, I guess.
我明白
I understand.
是吗
Do you?
你明白我在这儿有自己的生活吗
Do you understand I have a life here?
有一个好男人爱着我
A good man that loves me...
一个我不想去伤害的男人
A man I don't want to hurt?
我知道
I know.
你知道我早晨一起来
And do you know you're the first thing I think about
就会想到你
when I wake up in the morning
临睡前还在牵挂着你吗
and the last thing before I go to sleep?
-忘掉这种事情很难  -是啊
- It's tough to let something like that go. - Yeah.
尤其如果你总跑来
Especially if you keep showing up here.
你是想让我离开吗
Are you saying you want me to leave?
我是说  如果你要留下来
I'm telling you that if you stay,
哪怕是背弃我信仰的一切
against everything I believe in,
我都会和你在一起
I would be with you.
但如果你要离开
But if you leave...
别再回来了
Don't come back.
我不能让你一边插足我的生活
I can't have you with one foot in my life
一边还在外面做...
and one foot out there doing...
你在做的事
whatever it is you do.
你那部分的生活我根本不了解
That life of yours I have no idea about.
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know about it.
相信我
Believe me.
这决定很重要
It's a big step.
对我还是对你
For me or you?
我们俩
Both.
我要好好想想
I...need to think about this.
你也要仔细想想
You need to think about this.
言语无法表达你对我有多么重要
Words will never cover what you mean to me --
这永远不会变  但是我们应该
What you'll always mean to me, but we should...
好好想想
Think about it.
好吧
Okay.
不如两天后
How about two days from now...
七点半左右见面
Around 7:30?
那时我该下班了
I'll be off work then.
只有一人来  我们就心领神会了
One of us will be here, and we'll know.
我们两个都没有来
Neither of us will be here...
结果不言自明
And we'll know.
或者我们俩都来了
Or both of us will be here...
我们就都明白了
And we'll know.
瞧瞧啊
Wow, will you look at that?
第九个废弃工厂了
Our ninth abandoned factory.
壮哉我大美利坚
Ain't that America?
如果还是白跑
Hey, what do you say, this doesn't pan out,
我们往回开一英里去正打折的
we head back to that beer-and-bacon happy hour
那家啤酒和培根店如何
about a mile back, huh?
等等  迪恩
Wait a minute, Dean.
这些流浪汉  他们是恶魔
Those derelicts, they're demons.
我能看清他们的真面目
I can see their true faces.
克劳力在外面安排了这么多眼线
Crowley's got that many hell monkeys outside,
里面至少安排了双倍的人手
he's got to have at least double inside.
天使的防护  我能感受到
And angel warding. I can feel it.
那么你  我加恶魔刀就不够喽
Well, you, me, and a demon knife ain't gonna cut it.
我来联系萨姆
Okay. I'll get Sam.
不  我们不需要萨姆
No. We don't need Sam.
但你刚说
But you just said --
如果萨姆想来  他早就来了
Look, if Sam wanted in, he'd be here, okay?
我有更好的主意
I got a better idea.
读得慢吗
Slow read?
龟速
Slowest.
盖思在哪
Where's Garth?
去补给物资  我不知道
Supply run? I don't know.
我不太注意他的动向
Sort of lost track of when he comes and goes.
你们需要我帮忙吗
You guys need help with something?
我在工作
I'm working here.
你气色很差
You look horrible.
是啊  谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
他说得对  你没事吧  凯文
He's right. Are you okay,Kevin?
没事
Fine.
我只是在忙这个
I'm just... in the middle of this.
有发现吗
And? Any luck?
你指破译半个石碑吗
Interpreting half a demon tablet?
没有
No.
我一无所获
I got nothing.
好吧  打起精神
All right, well, buck up,
我们迫切需要点恶魔炸药
'cause, uh, we need some more of that demon TNT asap.
你都用光了吗
You used it all?
是啊  所以再做一批吧
Yeah, so let's whip up another batch.
好的
Sure.
约旦河西岸的金缕梅  埃及牛的头盖骨
West Bank witch hazel, skull of Egyptian calf,
不知道是否
the tail of some random-ass newt
已经灭绝了的蝾螈尾巴
that may or may not be extinct --
好了  好了  我懂了
All right, all right, I get it --
材料很难找到  对吧
Ingredients are hard to come by, huh?
还不止这三种材料呢
That's just the first three ingredients.
告诉我要什么  我去弄
Give me the list. I'll get what we need.
你还需要什么  维果
What on earth could you possibly need now, Viggo?
我把人类所有的刑具都给了你
I've given you every torture instrument known to man --
就差尼尔・戴蒙德的专辑了
Short of a Neil Diamond album.
60年代流行歌手
我有所发现  先生  我需要个翻译
I've found something, sir. I need a translator.
我就可以
You're looking at him.
展示给我看
Show me.
[天使语]
Zoh-bah-leh-ta.
这是什么情况
What have we here?
我想这是天使语
I think it's enochian.
当然是天使语  笨蛋
Of course it's enochian, you pigeon.
问题是  他为什么说起天使语了
The question is, why is he speaking enochian?
你钻到了什么  维果
What have you drilled into here, Viggo, huh?
[天使语]
Zoh-bah-leh-ta.
Sah-teh-voch-leh.
该死
Bollocks.
先生  他说什么
What is it, sir?
我们的小天使说的  差不多就是
What our feathered friend was uttering essentially was,
"你们这些天国的生命
"You, celestial being,
是被创造出来服侍主的天使"
have been created to be an angel of the lord."
你进入了他的控制系统
You've got into his operating system --
他的出厂设置
His factory settings.
从谁那里呢  上帝
From who? God?
谁在乎这是从哪来的
Who the hell cares where it comes from?
我们来瞧瞧这个飞猴是怎么工作的
Let's find out what makes this flying monkey tick.
[天使语]
Sah-teh-voch-leh.
不是吧
I mean, come on.
从埃及弄个小牛头骨能要多久啊
How long's it take to get a calf skull from Egypt?
凯文
Kevin.
你妈很性感
Your mom's hot.
真的  你妈妈是个性感的...
I'm serious, your mom is one sexy --
不是让你藏起来吗
Hey, I thought I told you to go underground.
我藏得可深呢
I am so far underground,
还在用稻草呼气呢 兄弟
I'm breathing through a straw, brother.
听着
Uh, look...
你朋友马丁那档子事
What happened with your friend Martin back there,
本不该是那个下场
it wasn't supposed to go down that way.
你孙女告诉我了
I know. Your granddaughter told me.
迪恩  你真的很够朋友
Dean, you did this old dog a real solid,
你为我挺身而出
and, uh...the way you stood up for me --
如果我俩互换位置  你也会这么做
Well, shoe on the other foot, you would have done the same.
是啊
Yeah.
我真不想再求你
I hate to ask for much else,
只是你会不会碰巧
but I don't suppose there's any chance
就在卡茨基尔附近呢
you're anywhere near the Catskills?
在美国另一头办事呢
Working a case on the other side of the country.
怎么了
Why? What's up?
就是有点难熬吧
Yeah, just hitting a little rough patch, I guess.
独自一人  你懂的
You know, doing this whole solo thing.
本尼  慢慢来
Benny... one day at a time, man.
你知道吗
You know what?
喝杯咖啡对会我很有帮助
Uh...A cup of coffee sure would do me good.
这件事一办完
All right, as soon as I'm done with this case,
我马上就来  好吗
I'll, uh... I'll be there, okay?
好的
Yeah.
兄弟  谢了
All right, brother. Thank you.
你妈在哪呢
Where is your mom?
一个安全的地方
Somewhere safe.
你把你妈撵走了
You kicked your mom to the curb?
她太让人分心了
She was too distracting.
我没法专心
I couldn't focus.
天使们说我必须去沙漠里
The angels said I had to go to the desert
学习神之语  对吧
to learn the word of God, all right?
这里就是我的沙漠
So... this is my desert.
但是你妈还是你妈啊
Yeah, but your mom's your mom.
我要拯救世界  就不能享乐
I can't enjoy a world I need to save, Dean.
等这一切都结束了再说吧
I can enjoy it when this is all over with.
而现在
For right now...
没有比这更重要的事了
There's nothing more important than this.
看着人类  永远都觉着新鲜  不是吗
Watching humanity -- it never gets old, does it?
我拿到了
I got what we need.
也该回来了
Oh, it's about time.
他来干什么
What's he doing here?
别担心  迪恩
Don't worry, Dean.
我们一救到阿尔菲  我就退出
Once we save Alfie, I'm out.
"我们"一救到阿尔菲
Oh, once "We" save Alfie.
可别伤到自己了  萨姆
Don't hurt yourself, Sam.
小卡和我能行
Cass and I can handle it.
小卡可不这么说
Not according to cass.
跟你说过我们不需要他
I told you we didn't need him.
我们需要一切可能的帮助  迪恩
We need everything, Dean.
而且我需要你们俩
And I need both of you,
像你们说的那样  把破事放一边
as you say, to stow your crap.
能办到吗
Can you do that?
这里有四个主护卫咒
So, there are four main points of warding --
北 南 东 西
North, south, east, and west --
四个天使语符号
And four enochian symbols,
像这样  你们得毁掉这些
like this, that you need to destroy
我才能进去
before I can enter.
好吧  然后呢
Okay, so, what?
我们进去  解决那些混蛋
We go in, take care of the hell mooks,
你去救出那个天使
and you extract the angel?
对
Yes.
我杀了那么多同胞
After killing so many,
我至少得救下这一个
I need to save at least this one.
听起来计划不错
Sounds like a plan.
好吧  动手吧
Okay. Let's do this.
等等  给你
Wait. Here.
这东西不仅对天使有用
This doesn't just work on angels.
也能杀死恶魔
It kills demons, too.
小卡  谢谢
Thanks, Cass.
套路有点老了  但是...
Well, not my most original work, but...
[天使语]
Voh-meh-pah-rah-less.
他说什么
What is it?
和石碑有关
That was tablet talk.
保护神之语
Protecting the word of God
似乎被根植到这些笨蛋的脑袋里了
seems to be hardwired into these dingbats.
谢了
Thanks.
走吧
Come on.
[天使语]
Zod-leh-fah.
"恶魔石碑"  说点我不知道的
"Demon tablet." Tell me one I don't know, huh?
阿尔菲
Alfie.
克劳力先生  并不是说这不重要
M-m-mr. Crowley, not that this isn't important,
但或许我们该准备离开了
but perhaps we should be making preparations to leave.
我们似乎受到了攻击
We -- we seem to be under attack.
你说什么了吗
Did you say something?
好了  小卡  出现吧
All right, anytime now, Cass.
小卡  你没事吧
Cass! Hey! You okay?
一定是因为这些魔符
It must be the sigils.
我的能量不够强
I'm not at full power.
萨姆  帮我把这东西涂了
Sam, help me muss this crud.
不  等等  没时间了
No, wait! There's no time.
萨曼德里奥坚持不了多久了
Samandriel won't last much longer.
小卡
Cass.
给  拿上这个
Here, take this.
迪恩  快点
Dean, hurry up.
开啊
Come on!
好吧  启用备用计划
All right. Plan "B."
我们有备用计划
We have a plan "B"?
你刚刚在说什么
As you were saying?
[天使语]
Bah-nah-sah-ee.
小卡  不帮我一把吗
Cass? Anytime now.
是吗
Yes?
[天使语]
Ar-doh-zah-feh.
快点说  你个天堂的废物
Spit it out, you heavenly pile of filth!
[天使语]
Pah-deh-rah.
我的天啊
Holy mother of sin.
什么  他说了什么
What? What is it?
还有一个天使之碑
There's an angel tablet.
别动
Hold still.
等下  我知道一些事
Wait! I know -- I know things.
小卡  快走
Cass! Go!
很好  你们有许多不知道的事
Good, good. There's so much you don't know.
你们需要我
You need me.
是吗
Yeah.
我不这么觉得
Yeah, I don't think so.
没关系  你现在安全了
It's okay. You're safe now.
我这就带你回家
I'm taking you home.
不  你不能带我回去  卡西迪奥
No. You can't take me back there, Castiel.
为什么不能
Why not?
你不明白
You don't understand.
我告诉了克劳力一些事
I told crowley... things --
一些他不应该知道的事
Things he shouldn't have known.
他知道了我们的密语  我们的秘密
He got to our coding, our secrets --
我都不知道我们知道的秘密
Secrets I didn't even know we had!
什么秘密
What secrets?
天堂  娜奥米
Heaven, Naomi.
不对  谁是娜奥米
No. W-who's Naomi?
谁是...
Who is --
听我说  认真听我说
Listen to me. Listen to me closely.
我去过  我知道
I've been there. I know!
卡西迪奥  他们在控制我们
They're controlling us, Castiel!
什么意思
What do you mean?
杀了他
Kill him!
他说"他们在控制我们"是什么意思
What does he mean, "They're controlling us"?
卡西迪奥
Castiel!
谁在控制我们  我怎么会看见你
Who is controlling us? Why did I see your face?
我那时为什么那么害怕  你对我做了什么
Why was I so afraid? What did you do to me?
这是命令  杀了他
This is a direct order! Kill him!
我刚刚做了什么
What did I just do?
你杀死了一个叛徒
You killed a traitor.
萨曼德里奥  是个好天使
Samandriel...was good.
我本想弥补之前的罪过
And I was trying to atone for --
萨曼德里奥叛变了
Samandriel was broken.
他泄露了我愿誓死去保护的东西的存在
He revealed the existence of what I would die to protect --
我们任何人都会誓死保护的秘密
What any of us would die to protect.
卡西迪奥  天使之碑
The angel tablet, Castiel.
克劳力知道了
Crowley knows.
我杀了一个天使就为了保护一块碑
I just murdered one of our own to protect a tablet?
如果恶魔之碑能把那群恶魔封在地狱里
If the demon tablet can seal demons in hell,
你觉得天使之碑对我们有什么作用
what do you think the angel tablet could do to us?
卡西迪奥  你是个英雄
You're a hero, Castiel.
你为天堂做了件大好事
You've done heaven a great service.
我跟萨姆和迪恩就是这么说的
And that's what I tell Sam and Dean?
小卡  发生了什么事
Cass! What the hell happened?
你告诉温彻斯特兄弟
You tell the Winchesters
萨曼德里奥变节了
that Samandriel had been compromised.
他变节了
He was compromised.
他袭击了你  你只得自卫
He came at you, and you acted in self-defense.
他袭击了我
He came at me.
我出于自卫杀了他
I killed him in self-defense.
你必须把他的肉身送回天堂
Say you must return his body to heaven,
然后带他来见我
and then bring him to me.
小卡  你还好吧
Cass, you okay?
我的肉身肯定是在混战中受伤了
My vessel must have been damaged in the melee.
我得走了
I have to go.
萨曼德里奥的遗体应该放在天堂
Samandriel's remains belong in heaven.
我得知道克劳力到底问出了多少东西
I need to see just how far Crowley dug into him.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
是的  我明白
Yes, I understand.
小卡  等等
Cass, wait.
谢谢你们俩
Thank you both...
谢谢你们做的一切
For everything you've done.
小卡
Cass!
好了  这样就行了
Okay. That should do it.
小卡现在看不到也听不到我们
Cass can't see or hear us now.
-到底怎么回事  -我知道
- Okay, what the hell? - I know.
我就说他从炼狱回来后
I told you something was off with him
有点不对劲
since he got back from purgatory.
怎么  你觉得有人在对他动手脚吗
So, what, you think someone's messing with him or something?
谁  天使吗
Who? Angels?
为什么天使要让他杀另一个天使
Why would the angels have him kill another angel?
这样吧  我来处理吧
You know what, man? I got this.
你走吧
You go.
什么
What?
不是有个女孩在等着你吗
Don't you have a girl to get back to?
是  我想是的
Yeah. I guess I do. Um...
你怎么会站在她那边了
Since when are you on the Amelia bandwagon?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我只是厌倦了这些争吵
I'm just tired of all the fighting.
而且  也许我有点小嫉妒
And, you know, maybe I'm a...little bit jealous.
我永远都不能像你那样把工作彻底抛开
I could never separate myself from the job like you could.
也许我们俩至少该有一个过得幸福点
Hell, maybe it's time for at least one of us to be happy.
你突然就接受这一切了吗
What, you being such a big hugger and all?
她确实能让我开心
She does make me happy,
如果我回去  说不定她正等着我呢
and she could be waiting for me if I went back.
如果是这样的话  我就太幸运了
I'd be a...very lucky man if she was.
但是现在
But now...
这一切的危机
With everything staring down at us,
还有那么多事要做
With all that's left to be done...
我不知道
I don't know.
是啊
Yeah.
但我知道这个
Well, I do know this
无论你的决定是什么  决定吧
whatever you decide...decide.
全情投入还是全身而退
Both feet in or both feet out.
如果你两者兼顾  会害死你的
Anything in between is what gets you dead.
是啊  有人跟我说了
Yeah, I keep hearing that.
我要出去走走  清醒一下头脑
I'm gonna...take a walk. Clear my head.
迪恩
Dean.
太谢谢你了  兄弟
Thank you mightily, bud.
我现在很艰难  你快到了吗
I'm in a hard way here. How close are you?
抱歉  我没法过去了
I'm sorry, man. I, um...I'm not gonna make it.
你的意思是现在  还是
You mean now, or...?
听着  本尼
Listen, Benny.
我永远不会忘记你为我做的一切
Everything you've done for me I will never forget,
但是
but, uh...
到此为止了
This is it.
就这样了
End of the line?
End of the line.
好吧  反正我也不喜欢这些手机
Yeah, well, I never liked these cellphones anyway.
你
You, uh...
你保重  好吗
You stay good, all right?
你也是  迪恩
You too, Dean.
另外
And, uh...
谢谢你带我出来
Thanks for the ride.
小事  兄弟
Yeah, man.
再见
Adios.